Narrator: 1
A: Did you know that Jake and Toby are cousins?
B: I had no idea! Oh well, you live and learn.
Narrator: 2
A: Are you any good with computers?
B: I know how to use one, but I don’t understand the ins and outs of how they work.
Narrator: 3
A: How’s your husband?
B: Much better, thanks. He hopes to be up and about by the weekend.
Narrator: 4
A: Did you sleep well last night?
B: Not really. I tossed and turned all night.
Narrator: 5
A: Are you going to accept that job offer?
B: I think I’ll have to. I’m not in a position to pick and choose.
Narrator: 6
A: What did the people do when the fire started?
B: They ran back and forth carrying buckets of water.
Narrator: 7
A: Is your football team top of the league?
B: Yes, but we aren’t home and dry yet, as we’ve got two more matches.
Narrator: 8
A: What was the weather like on your walk?
B: It was miserable. It rained on and off all day.